

Amornchai Kanokpullwad

Software Developer

website = www.zoonref.com

linkedin = www.linkedin.com/in/zoonref

Summary

Experienced engineer who create applications with love and focus on user happiness. I have been creating mobile/web applications for 5 years. I also have some sense of UI/UX design and addicted to making and using the app with good design. Quick learner and always learn something new.

Experiences

5 years work with companies to create product from the ground up.



株式会社ナナメウエ - Software Engineer (iOS/Android) 2015/11 - Present http://nanameue.jp

- Lead and train junior android engineers.
- Develop and maintain social network applications for Android.
- Implement WebRTC library for both Android and iOS to make voice and video call possible in company app.
- Improve development process of the team by using Gitflow, CI.



Goomeeki - Software Engineer (iOS/Android) 2014/9 - 2015/10 http://gomeeki.com

- Work in a team of developers to create iOS and Android application on both phone and tablet.
- Develop and maintain e-commerce shopping apps for iOS and Android



Dezainwerkz - Software Engineer 2013/9 - 2014/8 http://dezainwerkz.com

- Develop Frontend, Backend, iOS and Android Application.
- Working closely with designer to create beautiful animation and pixel-perfect user interfaces.
- Create RESTful API using Django with python.
- Create website using Angular framework.

Latest Projects



CallStats.io SDK for iOS

Library for sending WebRTC stats to CallStat.io written in Swift https://github.com/nanameue/callstats-ios



ひま部 for Android

Social network for student in Japan (99% Crash-free) https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.shuapps.himabu



Bitcoin Pebble Watchface

Bitcoin price checker for Pebble

https://apps.getpebble.com/en_US/application/57cc2c33be5ad0d9500002cd

Skills

iOS Development = Swift, Objective-C, CoreData, AutoLayout
Android Development = Kotlin, Java, RxJava, Realm
Web Development = Electron, ReactJS, RxJS, HTML, CSS, Flexbox
Other = Git, WebRTC, JWT

Certifications



Certified Bitcoin Professional (CBP)

2016/9 - 2018/9

http://cryptoconsortium.org



Cisco Certified Network Associate Routing & Switching (CCNA)

2010/6 - 2013/6

http://cisco.com

Education



King Mongkut's Institute of Technology Ladkrabang - 3.29

Bachelor of Science – Information Technology

2008 - 2012 http://kmitl.ac.th/en

- President of IT Forge club (Academy)
- Member of selected music bands to represent the institute
- Teacher Assistant in Java/JavaEE class room

Languages

Thai = Native

English = Conversational

Japan = Beginner